[
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct option related to Android.",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Android is an Operating System",
        "options": [
            "Android is a web browser",
            "Android is an Operating System",
            "Android is a web server",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is an activity in android?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) A activity is a single screen in an application.",
        "options": [
            "android class",
            "android package",
            "A single screen in an application with supporting java code",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    null,
    {
        "question": "Among the following options choose the one for which Android is based on Linux.",
        "answer": "Answer - D)  All of the above are reasons for which Android is based on Linux.",
        "options": [
            "Networking",
            "Portability",
            "Security",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Among the below virtual machines choose the one which is used by the Android operating system",
        "answer": "Answer - A)  Android uses Dalvik operating system.",
        "options": [
            "Dalvik operating system",
            "JVM",
            "Simple virtual machine",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the language on which Android is based upon.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Android is based upon Java.",
        "options": [
            "Python",
            "C++",
            "Java",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "All layout classes are the subclasses of",
        "answer": "Answer - C) all layout classes are the subclasses of android.view.ViewGroup in android.",
        "options": [
            "android.widget",
            "android.view.View",
            "android.view.ViewGroup",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The full form of APK is",
        "answer": "Answer - C) APK stands for Android package kit.",
        "options": [
            "Android Page Kit",
            "Android Phone Kit",
            "Android Package Kit",
            "Android Photo Kit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is manifest XML in android?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) It has all the information about an application",
        "options": [
            "It has information about layout in an application",
            "It has all the information about an application",
            "It has the information about activities in an application",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the use of a content provider in Android?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) A content provider is used to share information between Android applications.",
        "options": [
            "For sharing the data between applications",
            "For storing the data in the database",
            "For sending the data from an application to another application",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "While developing android application developers can test their apps on",
        "answer": "Answer - D) Apps can be tested in all the sources mentioned above.",
        "options": [
            "Emulators in Android SDK",
            "Android Phone",
            "Third-Party Emulator",
            "All the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In android, mini activities are also known as",
        "answer": "Answer - C) In android, mini activities are also known as Fragments",
        "options": [
            "Adapter",
            "Activity",
            "Fragments",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Among the following choose the one which converts Java bytecode into Dalvik bytecode",
        "answer": "Answer - A)  dex compiler converts convert JAVA bytecode into Dalvik bytecode.",
        "options": [
            "dex compiler",
            "Mobile interpretive compare",
            "Dalvik converter",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The services in android can be stopped using which of the following method?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) stopSelf() and stopService() method can be used to stop services in android.",
        "options": [
            "system. exit()  method",
            "stopSelf() and stopService() method",
            "finish() method",
            "end() method"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Activity in Android can be killed using?",
        "answer": "Answer - D) Activity in Android can be killed using both finishActivity (int requestCode) and finish() method.",
        "options": [
            "finishActivity (int requestCode)",
            "finish() method",
            "neither a and b",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The full form of ADB is.",
        "answer": "Answer - B)  ADB stands for Android debug Bridge.",
        "options": [
            "Android Delete Bridge",
            "Android Debug Bridge",
            "Android Destroy Bridge",
            "Android Developed Bridge"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AVD stands for",
        "answer": "Answer - C) AVD stands for Android virtual device",
        "options": [
            "Active Virtual Display",
            "Android Virtual display",
            "Android Virtual Device",
            "Active Virtual Device"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the option which is contained in the src folder",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Java source code is contained in the src folder",
        "options": [
            "Manifest",
            "Java Source Code",
            "XML",
            "All of them"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the parent class of activity.",
        "answer": "Answer - A) The contextThemeWrapper class is the parent class of activity.",
        "options": [
            "contextThemeWrapper",
            "context",
            "object",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose among the following tabs in which an error is shown",
        "answer": "Answer - D) Logcat shows an error.",
        "options": [
            "ADB logs",
            "Memory",
            "CPU",
            "Logcat"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "When was Open Handset Alliance announced?",
        "answer": "Answer - D) Open Handset Alliance was announced in 2007",
        "options": [
            "2004",
            "2005",
            "2006",
            "2007"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the topmost layer of Android architecture",
        "answer": "Answer - B) The topmost layer of Android architecture is the application framework.",
        "options": [
            "Applications",
            "Applications Framework",
            "Linux Kernel",
            "System libraries and android runtime"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the lowest layer of Android architecture.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Linux kernel Is the lowest layer of Android architecture.",
        "options": [
            "Applications",
            "Applications framework",
            "Linux Kernel",
            "System libraries and android runtime"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify among the following which is not a state in the service lifecycle.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Paused is not a state in the service lifecycle.",
        "options": [
            "Running",
            "Start",
            "Paused",
            "Destroyed"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the dialogue class in Android among the following",
        "answer": "Answer - D) All of the above are dialogue classes in Android.",
        "options": [
            "DatePicker Dialog",
            "AlertDialog",
            "ProgressDialog",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the built-in database of Android.",
        "answer": "Answer - B) SQLite Is the built-in database of Android.",
        "options": [
            "MySQL",
            "SQLite",
            "Oracle",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the one which provides access to the database.",
        "answer": "Answer - B) android.database provides access to the database.",
        "options": [
            "android.api",
            "android.database",
            "android.content",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is.sendStickybroadcast(intent) used?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) sendStickybroadcast(intent) is used to show intent is sticky.",
        "options": [
            "To show intent is prioritize",
            "To show intent is optional",
            "To show intent is sticky",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify among the one which is used to log debug messages.",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Log.d() is used to log debug messages.",
        "options": [
            "Log.R()",
            "Log.d()",
            "Log.D()",
            "Log.r()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The full form of ANR is.",
        "answer": "Answer - B) ANR stands for Application not responding",
        "options": [
            "Application not rendering",
            "Application not responding",
            "Application not reacting",
            "Application not reachable"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "All layout classes are subclasses of which of the following?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) All layout classes are subclasses of android .view.Viewgroup",
        "options": [
            "android.widget",
            "android.view.view",
            "android .view.Viewgroup",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the layout in which Android arranges its children into rows and columns.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) TableLayout arranges its children into rows and columns.",
        "options": [
            "FrameLayout",
            "RelativeLayout",
            "TableLayout",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The full form of GCM is",
        "answer": "Answer - B) GCM stands for Google Cloud messaging",
        "options": [
            "Google Centre messaging",
            "Google Cloud messaging",
            "Google account",
            "None account manager"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct definition of the nine-patch images tool in Android",
        "answer": "Answer - A) Nine-patch images tool is used to change the bitmap images into 9 sections.",
        "options": [
            "Used to change the bitmap images in 9 sections",
            "it is an image extension tool",
            "Neither a and b",
            "Both a and b"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "JSON stands for ___________",
        "answer": "Answer - C) JSON stands for Javascript Object Notation.",
        "options": [
            "JavaScript Oriented Notation",
            "JavaScript Object Native",
            "JavaScript Object Notation",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct option to find the JSON element length in Android JSON.",
        "answer": "Answer - D) To find the JSON element length in Android JSON, length() is used.",
        "options": [
            "sum()",
            "add()",
            "count()",
            "length()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Transient data in Android is.",
        "answer": "Answer - D) Transient data in Android is logical data.",
        "options": [
            "Secure data",
            "Permanent data",
            "Temporary data",
            "Logical data"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "On what is Android web browser-based?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Android web browser is based upon open-source WebKit.",
        "options": [
            "Safari",
            "Firefox",
            "Open-source WebKit",
            "Chrome"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Why is the view pager used?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) viewpager is used for swiping fragments.",
        "options": [
            "Paging down list items",
            "Swiping Fragments",
            "Swiping Activities",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "On which kernel is Android-based on",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Android is based on Linux.",
        "options": [
            "Windows",
            "Mac",
            "Linux",
            "Redhat"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the correct technique to refresh the dynamic content in Android.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Using the ajax technique we can refresh the dynamic content in Android.",
        "options": [
            "Java",
            "Android",
            "Ajax",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Under which, an open-source license is Android licensed?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Android is licensed under Apache/MIT.",
        "options": [
            "OSS",
            "Apache/MIT",
            "Gnus GPL",
            "Sourceforce"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "OHA stands for ___________.",
        "answer": "Answer - A) OHA stands for Open Handset Alliance.",
        "options": [
            "Open Handset Alliance",
            "Open Handset Association",
            "Open Handset Application",
            "Open Host Application"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of the following is the Android application Framework provided?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Android application Framework is provided in the Jar file.",
        "options": [
            "Zip file",
            "Jar file",
            "Object file",
            "EXE file"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following packages is used for supporting SQL libraries in the Android framework.",
        "answer": "Answer - C) javax.*  is used for supporting SQL libraries in the Android framework.",
        "options": [
            "android.*",
            "org.w3c.dom",
            "javax.*",
            "junit.*"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "WAP stands for?",
        "answer": "Answer - A) WAP stands for wireless application protocol.",
        "options": [
            "Wireless Application Protocol",
            "Wireless Application Program",
            "Wireless Application Portal",
            "Wireless Application Parts"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Choose the option below which are part of the system library and android runtime layer of Android architecture.",
        "answer": "Answer - D) SSL, DVM, and WebKit are all part of the system library and android runtime layer of Android architecture.",
        "options": [
            "SSL",
            "DVM",
            "Webkit",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who manages data sharing between applications?",
        "answer": "Answer - C) Data sharing between applications is managed by content providers.",
        "options": [
            "Telephony managers",
            "Location manager",
            "Content providers",
            "Activity manager"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Who develops DVM?",
        "answer": "Answer - A) DVM was developed by Dan Bornstein.",
        "options": [
            "Dan Bornstein",
            "Dennis Ritchie",
            "Linus Torvald",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a WebKit?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) Webkit is a browser engine.",
        "options": [
            "Database Server",
            "Browser Engine",
            "Database Engine",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "AAPT stands for",
        "answer": "Answer - C) AAPT stands for Android asset packaging tool.",
        "options": [
            "Android activity packaging tool",
            "Android action packaging tool",
            "Android asset packaging tool",
            "None"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Full form of NDK is _______",
        "answer": "Answer - B) NDK stands for Native Development Kit.",
        "options": [
            "Native Development Key",
            "Native Development Kit",
            "New Development Kit",
            "Net Development Kit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which language is used by WAP?",
        "answer": "Answer - B) WAP uses WML.",
        "options": [
            "SGML",
            "WML",
            "XML",
            "HTML"
        ]
    }
]